Po Ah Wong (Oscar)

Software Engineer

Mobile: 0415-167-868 | Email: wongpoah@gmail.com | Website: oscarwong.info Github: www.github.com/PoAhWong | LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/po-ah-wong

EXPERIENCE

Full-Stack Engineer

Redite Cyber and Data

Aprl 2022 to Current

- Coding, debugging, testing and troubleshooting throughout the development process.
- Design and implement new web applications for clients.
- Collaborates with clients and cross-functional develop team to understand requirements and translates requirements into real webpages or web applications
- Data Migration for clients by using data factory pipeline integration and data lake implementation of Azure.

Training Software Engineer

General Assembly

Jan 2022 to Apr 2022

After I figured out what my true passionate is, I spent every single minute to explore the coding world. I learnt web development and computer science fundamentals from this great institution during this 3 month full time bootcamp. And I implemented those new skills in my projects.

Assistant Accountant

Australia Cenvic Construction

Mar 2018 to Nov 2021

Collaborated within a finance team of 3, with strong detail focusing and communication skills, well completed a large project in Footscray. Built up skillsets of results driven, detail oriented, customer service, teamwork, time management.

PERSONAL SUMMARY

A highly motivated Software Engineer with an Accounting background, who has built up strong problem solving, detail oriented and communication skills within past years working experiences, and well combined these skills into software development area.

SKILLS

- JavaScript, React, Node, Express, Jest Unit Test, HTML, CSS
- PHP, Python, Ruby, Sinatra
- RESTful API, WebHooks
- Git, Azure, GCP, CI/CD Pineline
- PostgreSQL, MySQL, Google Firebase

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

General Assembly

Software Engineering Immersive Jan 2022 - Apr 2022

La Trobe University

Master of Accounting and Financial Management Mar 2014 - July 2016